

A customer-oriented Flight Attendant with six years of experience and over 3,000 domestic and international flight hours. A proven track record of calming passengers during emergency landings, performing CPR, and ensuring compliance with flight safety protocols.

## Professional Experience

#### Corporate Cabin Attendant

Delta Airlines, San Francisco, CA| October 2020 - Present

- Review private jet customer profiles, provide accommodations according to passenger needs, and identify opportunities to enhance the flight experience
- Deliver quality service to private and business jets with up to 50 passengers and prepare and serve upscale food and beverages to VIP clients
- Provide accommodations for individual needs, and maintain a 90% satisfaction score
- Attend regular flight safety tracking for both large and small business jets

#### Flight Attendant

Delta Airlines, San Francisco, CA| June 2017 - October 2020

- Provided exceptional service to passengers on both domestic and international flights and collaborated with flight attendants and pilots during pre-flight briefings to discuss weather conditions, service plans, and safety protocols
- Developed and delivered engaging pre-flight safety presentations to passengers and utilized upselling techniques to increase food sales by 15%

San Francisco, CA 12345 anth onygent i le@exa mple.co m (123) 456-7890 Linkedin I Portfolio

#### Education

# Bachelor of Arts (BA) Tourism & Hospitality

University of San Francisco, San Francisco, CA September 2013 - June 2017

### Key Skills

- ♦ Flight Safety
- Customer Service
- ♦ Conflict Resolution
- · Emergency Medical Care
- Italian (Fluent)

#### Certifications

- FI igh t Attendant Certifi cate of Demonstrated Proficiency, FAA, 2016
- CPR Certified, American Heart Association, 2016